<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Think\'der</string>
    <string name="Welcome">Welcome to Think\'der</string>
    <string name="Start">Start your journey to the</string>
    <string name="Start2">World of Ideas</string>
    <string name="search_title">Search</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search Thinkers</string>
    <string name="feedback_link"><a href='http://goo.gl/forms/FRNzxISE5p'>http://goo.gl/forms/FRNzxISE5p</a></string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_first_thinker">Hermann Hesse</string>
    <string name="hesse">Hermann Hesse</string>
    <string name="hesse_stats">Hermann Hesse\n(1877-1962)\n</string>
    <string name="hesse_most">Works\n\nSiddhartha  (1922)\nSteppenwolf  (1927)\nThe Glass Bead Game  (1943)</string>
    <string name="hesse_more">A prized author from 1920s Germany and a 1960s United States counterculture icon would be a strange way to describe any author other than Hermann Hesse. The loss of moral and spiritual fiber that Hesse perceived in the world around him after World War I survived past his years and was made popular again in the wake of the 1960s counterculture movement in the US. His novels sharply focus on the <b>search for meaning in life</b> and its opposition to the goals of modern society.</string>
    <string name="hesse_quote">"“Whoever wants music instead of noise, joy instead of pleasure, soul instead of gold, creative work instead of business, passion instead of foolery, finds no home in this trivial world of ours.”"</string>
    <string name="more_info">MORE INFO</string>
    <string name="butler">Judith Butler</string>
    <string name="butler_stats">Judith Butler\n(1956-Present)\n</string>
    <string name="butler_most">Works\n\nGender Trouble  (1990)\nImitation and Gender Insubordination  (1990)</string>
    <string name="butler_more">Butler\'s big idea is that behaviors seen as masculine or feminine aren\'t based on anything "natural". Sure there are biological differences, but genders only act in certain ways because of stereotypes that are repeated so often that they worm their way into cultural consciousness. Women don\'t have to wear lipstick; men don\'t have to like watching wrestling; we\'re just used to thinking that because we see it so often. And when people "perform" the acts that fit those assumptions, they produce what\'s seen as the reality of how people "are" (the ontology).</string>
    <string name="butler_quote">"“That the gendered body is performative suggests that it has no ontological status apart from the various acts which constitute its reality.”"</string>
    <string name="nietzsche">Friedrich Nietzsche</string>
    <string name="nietzsche_stats">Friedrich Nietzsche\n(1844-1900)\n</string>
    <string name="nietzsche_most">Works\n\nHuman, All Too Human  (1878)\nThus Spoke Zarathustra  (1885)\nBeyond Good and Evil  (1886)\nEcce Homo  (1908)</string>
    <string name="nietzsche_more">Nietzsche\'s fame and influence spanned across the fields of study from psychoanalysis to art to philosophy. His rejection of absolute truths, condemnation of all types of morality, and strict pessimism regarding the meaning of life are all part of what is now known as <b>nihilism</b>. His brand of nihilism is most famously known for its conclusion that each individual should have the courage to develop his own good and evil, independent of the society around him, and listen to nothing else.</string>
    <string name="nietzsche_quote">"“Convictions are more dangerous enemies of truth than lies.”"</string>
    <string name="rand">Ayn Rand</string>
    <string name="rand_stats">Ayn Rand\n(1905-1982)\n</string>
    <string name="rand_most">Novels\nWe the Living (1936)\nThe Fountainhead (1943)\nAtlas Shrugged (1957)\n\nNon-fiction\n For the New Intellectual (1961)\nThe Virtue of Selfishness (1964)\nCapitalism: The Unknown Ideal (1966)\n</string>
    <string name="rand_more">For Ayn Rand, it was more reasonable to act in one\'s own self-interest rather than in the interest of others. Her philosophy, known as Objectivism, describes man as a heroic being, whose moral purpose is his own happiness, and whose only absolute is reason. For Rand, once one accepted reason as the arbiter of all things, egoism and capitalism, would follow easily.</string>
    <string name="rand_quote">"“I am not primarily an advocate of capitalism, but of egoism; and I am not primarily an advocate of egoism, but of reason. If one recognizes the supremacy of reason and applies it consistently, all the rest follows.”"</string>
    <string name="wilde">Oscar Wilde</string>
    <string name="wilde_stats">Oscar Wilde\n(1854-1900)\n</string>
    <string name="wilde_most">Primary Works\n\n Ravenna (1878)\nIntentions (1891, essays and dialogues on aesthetics)\nThe Picture of Dorian Gray (1890)\n\nScholarship\n\nPetra Dierkes-Thrun, Salome’s Modernity: Oscar Wilde and the Aesthetics of Transgression (2011)\nKerry Powell and Peter Raby, Oscar Wilde in Context (2014)\nPeter Raby, The Cambridge Companion to Oscar Wilde (1997)</string>
    <string name="wilde_more">This statement exemplifies Wilde’s belief in “art for art’s sake,” that is in the fact that art – here, literature – does not have to serve any moral purpose and cannot be judged by that standard. The quote can be read both as Wilde’s direct response to his critics, and expression of Wilde’s overall aesthetic philosophy. Instead of measuring and judging literature against black-and-white “moral” or “immoral” standards, Wilde suggests, books have to be evaluated by different, wholly literary, standards, i.e. by looking at their performance and brilliance in terms of style and overall aesthetics: are they “well written,” or “badly written”</string>
    <string name="wilde_quote">"“There is no such thing as moral or an immoral book. Books are well written, or badly written. That is all.”"</string>
    <string name="zhuangzi">Zhuangzi</string>
    <string name="zhuangzi_stats">Zhuangzi\n(369-286 BCE)\n</string>
    <string name="zhuangzi_most">The Zhuangzi (3rd century BCE)</string>
    <string name="zhuangzi_more">The butterfly dream, as this story is called, showcases one of Zhuangzi\'s core beliefs: the idea that the enlightenment comes when a person becomes unbounded, like a butterfly, floating freely, being one with heaven, and not with emotional or material attachments to the earth. In this case, Zhuangzi is showing us that to be enlightened from a grounded man to a freely floating butterfly, one must transform their mind, and that this transformation is similar to waking up from a lifelong dream.</string>
    <string name="zhuangzi_quote">"“Once upon a time, I, Zhuangzi, dreamt I was a veritable butterfly, fluttering hither and thither, enjoying itself to the full of its bent, and not knowing it was Zhuangzi. Suddenly I awoke, and came to myself, the veritable Zhuangzi. Now I do not know whether it was then I dreamt I was a butterfly, or whether I am now a butterfly dreaming I am a man. Between me and the butterfly there must be a difference. This is an instance of transformation.”"</string>
    <string name="aurelius">Marcus Aurelius</string>
    <string name="aurelius_stats">Marcus Aurelius\n(121-180)\n</string>
    <string name="aurelius_most">Works\n The Thoughts of the Emperor Marcus Aurelius Antoninus (2nd century CE)\n\nScholarship\nC.R. Haines, Marcus Aurelius (1930)\nP. A. Brunt, Marcus Aurelius in his Meditations. (1974)\nP. Hadot, The Inner Citadel: The Meditations of Marcus Aurelius (1998)</string>
    <string name="aurelius_more">Being the emperor of Rome, Aurelius had to deal with a multitude of problems that came up in the course of, well, ruling an Empire which spanned the landmass of 40 modern-day countries. Using intense self-reflection, he coped with stress by utilizing stoic principles to prevent external influences from hampering his thinking.</string>
    <string name="aurelius_quote">"“Very little is needed to make a happy life; it is all within yourself, in your way of thinking.”"</string>
    <string name="socrates">Socrates</string>
    <string name="socrates_stats">Socrates\n(469-399 BCE)\n</string>
    <string name="socrates_most">Primary Sources\n\nPlato, Symposium (4th century BCE)\nPlato, Apology (4th century BCE)\n Plato, Phaedo (4th century BCE)\n Plato, Euthyphro (4th century BCE)</string>
    <string name="socrates_more">Socrates believed that inquiry and thought about why we think of things as we do was the essence of life. That unless we understand why the world seems different to me than it does to my neighbor, we cannot understand life itself. Destroying this illusion that we already comprehend the world perfectly and honestly accepting the fact of our own ignorance, Socrates believed, were vital steps toward our acquisition of genuine knowledge. Only by discovering universal definitions of the key concepts governing human life, could we truly examine what human life is. This realization is often cited as the birth of Greek philosophy.</string>
    <string name="socrates_quote">"“The unexamined life is not worth living.”"</string>
    <string name="spinoza">Baruch Spinoza</string>
    <string name="spinoza_stats">Baruch Spinoza\n(1632-1677)\n</string>
    <string name="spinoza_most">Works\nEthics (1677)\nTheological-Political Treatise (1677)\n\nRecommended Secondary Literature in English\nHenry Allison, Benedict de Spinoza: An Introduction (1987)\nYitzhak Melamad and Michael A. Rosenthal, Spinoza\'s Theological-Political Treatise: A Critical Guide (2010)</string>
    <string name="spinoza_more">Albert Einstein once said, "“I believe in Spinoza\'s God, who reveals himself in the lawful harmony of the world, not in a God who concerns himself with the fate and the doings of mankind.”"; he later expanded on his comments about Spinoza\'s and his own ideas on religion elsewhere : "“I can understand your aversion to the use of the term "religion" to describe an emotional and psychological attitude which shows itself most clearly in Spinoza … I have not found a better expression than \'religious\' for the trust in the rational nature of reality that is, at least to a certain extent, accessible to human reason.”"</string>
    <string name="spinoza_quote">"“My opinion concerning God differs widely from that which is ordinarily defended by modern Christians. For I hold that God is of all things the cause immanent, as the phrase is, not transient.”"</string>
    <string name="angelou">Maya Angelou</string>
    <string name="angelou_stats">Maya Angelou\n(1928-2014)\n</string>
    <string name="angelou_most">Autobiographies\nI Know Why the Caged Bird Sings (1969)\nGather Together in My Name (1974)\nMom &amp; Me &amp; Mom (2013)\n\nPoetry\nAnd Still I Rise (1978)\nShaker, Why Don\'t You Sing? (1983)\nI Shall Not Be Moved (1990)\n""On the Pulse of Morning"" (1993)</string>
    <string name="angelou_more">As an African-American female writer in the 1960s, Angelou was writing in a society where her voice and her personal experiences could have been easily marginalized. Many African-American writers were concerned with how to write works which could be accepted by society, how to reason people into seeing the racial issues which plagued the country. Instead, Angelou tackled issues of racism and childhood abuse through a form of honest, confessional writing dominated by emotional appeals to the reader, a style focused on relating the stories of the marginalized and abused with pride rather than shame.</string>
    <string name="angelou_quote">"“The idea is to write it so that people hear it and it slides through the brain and goes straight to the heart.”"</string>
    <string name="works">WORKS</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fragment_container">FragmentContainer</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hesse_next_level">HesseNextLevel</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
